blogged.com 2013-05-16

# Privacy Policy | Chime.In

UberMedia is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store and use information from and about users of our websites, including www.ubermedia.com, www.chime.in, www.ubersocial.com, and www.echofon.com (the “Sites”), and any services or software available or enabled via the Sites (“Services”). This Privacy Policy is subject to our [Universal Terms](http://ubermedia.com/all-terms/terms). By using our Sites or Services, you expressly consent to UberMedia’s collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with anything in this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Sites or the Services. 

## INFORMATION COLLECTED

  1. **_Automatic Collection:_ ** Like most other websites, we use common internet technologies such as _cookies_ and _Web beacons_ to keep track of users’ interactions with the Sites and the Services. This may include your _internet protocol (IP) address, referring website addresses, browser type and access times._ A glossary that explains each of these italicized terms is included at the end of this Privacy Policy. If you use the Services, we may also collect data related to your use of the application and the device on which the application is loaded. 
  2. **_Volunteered:_ ** If you register with us, fill out a profile page, purchase products or services, send us an email, or share personal information with us in any other way, we will collect and store whatever information you share. This obviously depends on what information you choose to provide but it may include your name, email address, credit card information or other billing information. You do not have to share this information with us, but without it you may not be able to access certain content or features or participate in certain areas of the Sites or Services. 
  3. **_Publicly Posted:_ ** If you post information on any public areas of the Sites (or elsewhere on the internet), that information may be collected, stored and used by anyone, including us. (We strongly recommend that you do not post any information that allows strangers to identify or locate you. Posting such information may result in unsolicited messages or contact from others, to say the least.) 
  4. **_Use of Social Media Applications:_ ** The Services utilize certain APIs, “feeds” or other mechanisms provided by third parties, including Twitter or Facebook as applicable (“Third Party Apps”), to access your accounts as authorized by you during your use of the Services and to display Content (as defined in our Terms) on your desktop or mobile device. The Third Party Apps work within the privacy settings of the account holders for such third party services and do not access Content, data or information not authorized by those privacy settings. Please refer to the privacy settings in your account to manage your public profile and other aspects of your account. 
  5. **_Mobile Location Information:_ ** If you have activated a mobile application and permitted your mobile or other location-aware device to transmit location data, we will collect and store information related to your mobile device location to help provide a better experience with our Services. Some functional use of the Services may be dependent on the data related to your geographic location and geopositional data. If the settings on your location-aware device allow us to receive location information, we may also associate location information with other information we have about you. 

## HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

The short answer is that we use information to help us provide you with better experience with the Sites and Services. It also helps our advertisers and partners provide you with more relevant offers. Among other things, the information we collect enables UberMedia to:

  * customize the advertising and content you see
  * fulfill your requests for products and services and validate your user rights
  * improve the Sites and Services
  * contact and communicate with you
  * conduct research and analysis
  * provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients
  * provide you with additional information we think is of interest to you

## WHEN DO WE SHARE OR DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION?

  * **Anonymous Information.** Anonymous information is information that does not identify you personally, like your IP address and referring website addresses. We may share anonymous information with others, such as advertisers, sponsors and business partners. 
  * **All Information (Both Anonymous and Personally Identifiable).** In certain circumstances, we may share any or all information we have collected, including personally identifiable information. For example: 

  * We might share your personally identifiable information during due diligence or in preparation for or after a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation.
  * If you give us permission, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties who might send you marketing and promotional information.
  * Your personal information may be transferred to anyone who is helping us make the Sites and Services available and functional, like technical agents, payment processing vendors, other subcontractors, and our affiliates and consultants.
  * As in any transaction, if you provide your credit card information to us for purchases, your credit card company will be provided with all relevant information about us, item(s) purchased, cost and other information necessary to process the transaction.
  * We may disclose your personal information if permitted or required by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend our interests or the interests of our users or business partners.

## CHILDREN UNDER 13

The Sites is not intended for children under age 13, or for anyone under age 18 without involvement of a parent or guardian. The Sites includes unmonitored content posted by users and sourced from other third parties and as you can imagine, such content may be unsuitable for children. We do not knowingly collect or distribute information from or about children under 13.

## THIRD PARTIES

  * Like most (maybe all) other websites, third parties may directly gather non-personally identifiable information from users of the Sites through automated means such as Cookies. For example, we may engage a third party to help us track and analyze anonymous information from users who visit the Sites or use the Services or the performance of advertisements. In addition, advertisers and ad-serving services may set Cookies or other automated mechanisms that gather anonymous information. This Privacy Policy does not cover how third parties use Cookies or other technologies or any information they gather through such technologies.
  * The Sites and Services may contain links to websites or other properties and content operated by third parties over which UberMedia has no control. Their privacy policies may be different from our Privacy Policy, and you access such linked websites or third-party content at your own risk.

## SECURITY

Information that UberMedia collects is stored on servers that UberMedia manages, using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information. Please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet or information contained in our servers can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, UberMedia cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Sites or Services and you do so at your own risk.

## FOREIGN COUNTRIES

Your personal information may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state or country or to a jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your location. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that UberMedia processes and stores information in the United States and your use of our Sites or Services constitutes your consent to and understanding of this processing.

## CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

UberMedia reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and will do so by posting changes to this Privacy Policy. The new Privacy Policy will apply to all current and past users of the Sites and will replace any prior Privacy Policies that are inconsistent.

## DISPUTE RESOLUTION

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California applicable to agreements made and performed in California, excluding the application of the conflict of laws provisions. You agree that any action or suit brought by a party to enforce or adjudicate your rights under this Agreement shall be brought in the federal or state courts located in Los Angeles, California.

## CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we have shared with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes in the past 12 months. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which such was shared. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: UberMedia, Inc.; Attn: Privacy Policy; 130 West Union Street; Pasadena, CA 91103. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response.

## CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or UberMedia’s privacy practices, please email us at [_privacy@ubermedia.com_](mailto:privacy@ubermedia.com).  
Or you can contact us by mail at:   
**UberMedia, Inc.** 130 West Union Street, Pasadena, CA 91103 

In addition, if you wish to exclude your personal information from our direct marketing, or if you would like to update or delete your email address, mailing address or other personal information, or otherwise manage communications your receive from UberMedia, please contact us at the above.   
“UberMedia” “We” and “Our” means UberMedia, Inc. and its subsidiaries.   
Effective: July 1, 2012

## Glossary

  * _Cookie_ : When you visit the Sites or utilize an UberMedia product or service, UberMedia’s servers send a cookie (a small file with a string of characters) to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you but they recognize your individual web browser or mobile address. Unless you choose to identify yourself to UberMedia (through an account or otherwise), you will remain anonymous to us. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies. However, if you do so, certain features may not work. 
  * _Web beacon_ : A web beacon is an electronic image on a web page that recognizes certain types of information on your computer when you visit that particular web page. 
  * _IP address_ : An Internet Protocol Address is a numerical label that is assigned to each computer on the Internet. 
  * _Referring website address_ : A referring website address identifies the address of the webpage you were on previously, before you came to the Sites. 
  * _Browser_ : A browser is a software application used for retrieving, presenting and traversing information resources on the World Wide Web.
